dvo.com 2006-10-18

# DVO Enterprises Privacy Policy

TOP SELLERS

Cook'n with Betty Crocker™ 

$29.95  

Cook'n Software Download

$39.95  

_Dan, Wow. This is a note to thank you for the nice welcome email. And to tell you I've been in the computer business for 20 years as programmer and network administrator. This is the first time I've seen such a sincere sounding CEO of a computer related business. The content was warm and very sincere. And I'd like to compliment you on the quality of your product. I only have Taste of Home right now, but I love the way you've put the software together. It's laid out very intuitively. Well, just wanted to thank you for the welcome and your products and your sincerity. Much good fortune with your venture. I support you._

Regards,  
Steve Van Wie 

NEWSLETTER

• Current Issue  
• Newsletter Archive   
• Contact Info

**DAILY SPECIAL**  
Order today and receive a FREE   
Breakfast Recipes CD!  
Find out how.

|    
DVO Enterprises is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its online visitors. None of your personal information will be sold or rented to other companies for any reason. This policy statement provides our visitors with an overview of the measures we have taken to provide a safe environment for everyone.

**PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

We consider the following, among other things, to be personally identifiable information: first and last name, e-mail address, street address and phone number. 

We may request such personally identifiable information from our visitors to process and fulfill orders for products or services and in connection with contests, sweepstakes, product registration, newsletter subscription, and visitors' requests for information. 

**NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND THE USE OF COOKIE TECHNOLOGY**

We collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of a software technology called "cookies," and through our visitors' voluntary submissions to us and/or upon our request. By non-personally identifiable information, we are referring to information about our visitors' browsers (e.g., Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer), operating systems (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), Internet service providers (e.g., AOL or NET.COM) and other similar information which we track in aggregate form.

Cookie technology helps us to know how many people visit us and where visitors go on our site. Cookies are small bits of information we send to your computer. Among other things, this non-personally identifiable information allows us to know which areas are favorites, which areas need a bit of improvement, or what technologies and Internet services are being used by our visitors so that we may continually improve our visitors' online experiences. 

**USE OF IP ADDRESSES**

We collect IP addresses to obtain aggregate information on the use of dvo.com. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by a Web server when you're on the Web. When you are on our site, we have a back-end server that logs your computer's IP address. We only use the information we find out from tracking IP addresses in the aggregate, such as how many users entered a specific area of our site, and not to track a specific IP address to identify an individual user. However, we may use such information to identify a user if we feel that there are or may be safety and/or security issues or to comply with legal requirements. 

**SECURITY**

DVO Enterprises ensures that all personally and non-personally identifiable information that it receives via the Internet is secure against unauthorized access. This information is kept in a safe and secure system isolated from direct connection to the Internet. This means that no eyes but ours will ever see the information that our visitors send to us, unless we indicate otherwise. We will give out personal information as required by law, for example to comply with a court order or subpoena or to assist in criminal investigations. We may also give out personal information when we deem it advisable in order to protect the safety and security of our sites and visitors to our sites. 

**Why are we so safe?**

DVO Enterprises uses secure server software over a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) line to protect your credit card information. It encrypts all of your personal and credit card information so that this information cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system, and once it is received, it is stored in a location not accessible via the Internet. 

* * *
